<!DOCTYPE idea-plugin PUBLIC "Plugin/DTD" "http://plugins.intellij.net/plugin.dtd">
<idea-plugin version="2">
  <name>Jetty Integration</name>
  <id>Jetty Integration</id>
  <description>Allows configuration and use of the Jetty webserver directly from IntelliJ IDEA, for running/debugging web applications.</description>
  <version>##PLUGIN_VERSION##</version>
  <depends>com.intellij.javaee</depends>
  <vendor email="mark@codebrewer.org" logo="/images/jetty16x16.png">Codebrewer</vendor>
  <change-notes>
    <![CDATA[<b>Version 0.4.1 (Build 54)</b>
<ul>
<li>Fixed: Updated version dependency information for compatibility with IDEA 8.1.</li>
</ul>
<b>Version 0.4.0 (Build 53)</b>
<ul>
<li>New: Support JSP debugging.</li>
<li>New: Detect Hightide installations when creating Jetty Application Server configurations.</li>
</ul>
<b>Version 0.3.1 (Build 51)</b>
<ul>
<li>New: Updated for IDEA 8.x.</li>
<li>Fixed: Launch scripts fail when Java executable path and Jetty configuration file paths contain spaces.</li>
<li>Fixed: Default order of configuration files when creating an application server configuration causes IllegalStateException.</li>
<li>Fixed: Jetty version number may not be detected correctly when creating an application server configuration.</li>
<li>Fixed: Launch process sometimes fails to determine stop port and key, preventing IDEA from stopping Jetty.</li>
</ul>
<b>Version 0.3.0 (Build 39)</b>
<ul>
<li>New: Support IDEA 7.x facets.</li>
<li>New: Support hot deployment of web contexts.</li>
</ul>
<b>Version 0.2.0 (Build 18)</b>
<ul>
<li>New: Permit Jetty's configuration files to be specified.</li>
<li>Fixed: plugins.intellij.net makes bundling source code with a binary distribution unnecessary.</li>
<li>Fixed: IDEA project files are not included in source code archive.</li>
</ul>
<b>Version 0.1.1 (Build 10)</b>
<ul>
<li>Fixed: plugins.intellij.net shows no plug-in description.</li>
<li>Fixed: jetty.bat fails when Jetty and IDEA are installed on different Windows drives.</li>
<li>Fixed: jetty.sh is not executable after plug-in installation.</li>
</ul>
<b>Version 0.1.0 (Build 7)</b>
<ul>
<li>Initial release</li>
</ul>]]>
  </change-notes>
  <idea-version since-build="##IDEA_VERSION_MIN##" until-build="##IDEA_VERSION_MAX##" />
  <resource-bundle>org.codebrewer.idea.jetty.JettyBundle</resource-bundle>
  <extensions defaultExtensionNs="com.intellij">
    <configurationType implementation="org.codebrewer.idea.jetty.JettyRunConfigurationType" />
    <javaee.appServerIntegration implementation="org.codebrewer.idea.jetty.JettyManager" />
  </extensions>
</idea-plugin>
